[crow cawing]
[Pani Bottle]
I wonder what card she'll play.
If she doesn't want to end it now,
she'll use it later.
Ah, maybe Jimin should've played it safe.
-But...
-Am I wrong?
...Jimin could boldly use
the Joker to win.
-Yeah.
-[Pani Bottle] If Horseking decides
to absolutely not play any card
other than the King...
-Yeah.
-...she can be aggressive.
What? I keep getting messages.
[♪ intriguing music playing]
[dealer] We will announce the results.
PARK JIMIN, HORSEKING
We will check the cards.
The winner is Horseking.
[Jimin groans]
[Horseking] I don't know
if my opponent has Joker,
but even if they do,
they'd never play it first.
That's the battle of wits.
Even if she has a Joker,
how could she possibly play it?
I thought it was the perfect move.
[exhales]
If I put down the Joker
and it gets taken, I'm done.
The pressure mounted, and I was going
to throw it away anyway,
so I decided to play the 4.
Geez, it was Horseking again.
I really want to send him home.
[sighs frustratedly]
PARK JIMIN
"I lost. Horseking must've played his 7.
I played my 4."
Why?
Did she play her 4?
They announced it?
[Pani Bottle] Then, the 4 is gone.
[clears throat]
[sighs] Playing the Joker was too risky.
-You played your 4, right?
-I did. He must've used his 7.
It's because he can't play
the King so easily.
He knows I might have the Joker.
[sighs]
When I heard she didn't play the Joker,
I was disappointed,
but I don't think
I could've played it either.
I think her thought was,
"Would he play the King right away
without knowing who has the Joker?"
At this point,
we really need to be running around.
The question is, who has the Joker?
-[Jaegyun] Yeah.
-[ZZONE] Right.
DDOLDDOL, JUNSEO, EUNSIL
JIMIN, PANI BOTTLE
You should keep an eye on Jimin.
-Me? I can just tag her?
-[Horseking] Yeah.
It's because I kind of have a feeling
that Jimin has the Joker.
[♪ thrilling music playing]
She knew I had the King
and played mind games with me.
He wouldn't play the King, right?
She said that.
Of course, it could've been a bluff.
But in any case, I took that as,
"I may have the Joker.
You sure you want to come at me?"
So it's likely Jimin has it.
Let's tag and beat her.
If she's not eliminated,
she's definitely the Joker.
-Right.
-Jimin's easy to tag. Let's start there.
-Then...
-[Jaegyun] Junseo.
Junseo's the only one with two cards.
Everyone else is clinging to one.
-That's why Junseo is protecting them.
-[ZZONE] Yeah.
[Horseking] We need to think
of getting rid of Junseo too.
BIGGEST THREAT TO BLUE TEAM IS JUNSEO
At this point,
you need to go after Junseo.
Nothing else matters.
You have an 8.
It's definitely higher than Junseo's card.
You need to play the 8.
[Dail] I had the highest card
after Horseking.
My assignment for our team
was to tag Yuk Junseo with my 8.
[Jaegyun] Dail, the best move
is to have you tag Junseo.
DAIL'S TARGET IS JUNSEO
Let's eliminate them one at a time now.
[alarm blaring]
I'll go to the reeds.
[Dail] Go to the right.
-[host] The Battle Round has begun.
-[Dail] Let's go.
[♪ thrilling music continues playing]
[Horseking] What?
[♪ music fades]
RED TEAM BASE, 2ND FLOOR
[♪ mysterious music playing]
RED TEAM IS HIDING
10 MINUTES AGO
I don't think we can look
for symbols right now.
We've only found one so far.
We should lie in wait here.
-We should just ambush them.
-Guerrilla warfare?
-We should stay here.
-Watch and guard them?
[Horseking] No one's coming out!
I think we can search around!
No one's coming out!
Same here!
[ZZONE] This is actually
a great opportunity.
[Joonsu] We should look for the symbols.
Where are they?
[Jaegyun] There's nothing.
This is driving me crazy.
[ZZONE] What?
Red.
Don't tag me. Don't tag me.
Please. [panting]
ZZONE found one!
[Jaegyun] Did you find it?
Bring it over carefully.
[Horseking] That's our third one.
Okay, go!
No one's coming out!
[Dail] Same here!
[exclaims]
BLUE TEAM DESTROYS THIRD SYMBOL
[♪ intriguing music playing]
[Junseo whispering]
They're coming close from there.
JOONSU APPROACHES RED TEAM BASE
[Jimin] I think we can beat Joonsu.
-Let's go over there.
-[Junseo] Want to go around back?
[♪ tense music playing]
[footsteps]
[Jimin] Hey, hide.
Follow me.
They're hiding here!
[Jimin] I think I can get Joonsu.
-[Joonsu] Jimin and Junseo. Two!
-[Jimin] Let's get him.
Let's get him. Shit.
-Oh, no.
-Run, run.
[ZZONE] Run, run!
[Dail] Who is it?
Junseo.
-[Dail] Yuk Junseo?
-Yes.
Tag Joonsu, and you win.
-Of course.
-[Joonsu] There are two!
YUK JUNSEO TARGETS JOONSU
There are two here!
Junseo was walking toward me,
so I thought, "Good, he came on his own."
I had to tag Junseo.
[Jimin] Quick, go get him. Go and tag him.
DAIL TARGETS JUNSEO
You'll beat Joonsu for sure.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[ZZONE] Tag, tag!
ZZONE TAGS JUNSEO
-[Junseo] Are you okay?
-[host] Tag confirmed.
-[Dail] I was supposed to tag him.
-What?
[♪ comical music plays]
[exhales] How could she
possibly forget that?
We talked about it
over 10 times in the meeting.
Horseking basically drilled that into us.
You need to go after Junseo.
You need to play the 8.
Dail, the best move
is to have you tag Junseo.
[Dail] It was something we all knew.
That was my mission.
But then suddenly,
ZZONE bumped into Junseo
as he was coming toward me.
She was screaming
as she cut in from the side.
I still don't get it.
[Jimin panting]
[Jimin] There's something odd about her.
She got told off by Dail.
-[Ddolddol] Why?
-She wasn't supposed to tag Junseo.
[dealer] Both players,
please hand in your cards.
Here you go.
ZZONE, YUK JUNSEO
[dealer] Yuk Junseo has won.
ZZONE'S 3 GOES TO JUNSEO
[ZZONE] I was really bummed.
What just happened?
That was out of nowhere.
[Dail] Why would ZZONE tag him?
He was already coming right toward me.
To be fair, we knew Junseo had a 7.
We did. We knew.
[Horseking] We had a plan,
so why would she tag him?
THEY COULD HAVE WON WITH DAIL'S 8
Well, she's on our team,
so we have to trust her.
For now,
it's not bad because if Junseo used his 7
and we played something lower,
we lose and Junseo takes the 3.
But we could've finished it just now.
[Jaegyun] It's okay, it's okay.
We can't help that now.
-We're winning.
-[Jaegyun] That's right.
I'm not blaming her or anything.
It was just weird.
-Let's think about that later.
-[Jaegyun] Exactly.
-Anyway, we need to win this game.
-[Horseking] Right.
[Dail] I just really didn't get it.
She has to be the Seeker.
It doesn't make sense
unless she's the Seeker.
What happened? Did you give it up?
-[ZZONE] I lost.
-[Dail] You lost?
I thought if I ran into him,
he wouldn't be able to stop me.
-What?
-I thought if I ran into him,
he wouldn't be able to stop me.
We're asking why you tagged him.
That was my mistake. [chuckles]
I'm sorry.
It's okay. It happens.
It happens.
We lowered Junseo's card at least.
That wasn't our main strategy.
I apologize. I'm sorry. [chuckles]
-Now, we have two possible scenarios.
-[Jaegyun exclaims]
[Horseking] He had the 7.
Now, he has a 7 and 3.
-[Dail] Or a 3 and something.
-[Horseking] Yeah.
So, the best thing
is for Dail to tag Junseo.
With your 8.
Just like before, I should tag him.
MEANWHILE, RED TEAM
[Pani Bottle]
Are we supposed to keep hiding?
[Ddolddol] They're looking for symbols
while we're hiding.
-[Pani Bottle] I know.
-Or should we all charge in?
Face them head-on?
Let's give it a try.
Even if we go aggressive,
they can never tag you.
I'll give it a shot.
-[alarm blaring]
-I'll just go for it. All or nothing.
[Jimin] You go first.
Ddolddol should lead the way.
[♪ thrilling music playing]
[Joonsu] They're coming out!
[players laugh]
Geez, he's so annoying.
They're in front of the gate.
[scoffs] I want to punch him.
[Jimin] Joonsu was on lookout duty.
One person! Pani Bottle!
There are four here!
Jimin and Junseo. Two!
HUMAN MEGAPHONE REPORTS EACH ROUND
He went, "Ddolddol, Jimin!"
That little brat.
[sighs frustratedly]
If I tag him, I'd take one card,
so I decided to tag Joonsu.
Ah, Joonsu!
-[Joonsu] Yes?
-I'm sick of it. I'm just sick of that.
Can't I just tag you once?
This is scary.
[Jimin] You can tag me!
[Joonsu exclaims]
This is scary! Horseking!
This is bait. They're baiting us.
Come out to the middle.
PLAYER SUBSTITUTION
-Come here and tag me.
-You go away. I'm doing this with Joonsu.
So come to the center. How can you expect
to take Joonsu over there?
-[Joonsu] Joonsu, Joonsu!
-Yes, Joonsu, Joonsu.
Hey, I said back up. I'm by myself.
We're not coming after you.
Why are you so worked up?
Look, I'm here by myself,
so you should back up.
It's not like we're trying to tag you.
We're just telling you.
If you want to do something,
come to the middle.
[Junseo] We couldn't just go ahead
and tag them.
The Blue Team's King,
Horseking, was there.
One wrong move,
and the King could take our card.
We both knew who each other's Kings were.
We knew Ddolddol
would try to come and tag us.
We couldn't just rush in and tag them.
THE TWO KINGS IN A STANDOFF
That's why time slowly started to pass.
[Jimin] Are we going to keep doing this?
We're at an advantage.
We have the upper hand.
We have no reason to go.
-I think there are four of them.
-There are four.
-The other one is Yang Dail.
-[Ddolddol] Four, right?
They keep telling me to come out,
so don't you think Dail is hiding?
[Joonsu] Where's Dail?
He went off by himself again.
[Dail] No one's here.
RED TEAM BASE
If I go through the main entrance,
I'll definitely get caught.
I was looking for another way in.
Then, I spotted this tiny opening
through the window.
So I went right through it.
SUCCESSFULLY INFILTRATES RED TEAM BASE
[Jimin] Let me tag you once!
PEEKING OUT
Let me tag you once!
Let's do something at least!
-This is ridiculous!
-[Joonsu] I can tag you?
[Jimin] Let me tag you one time!
[Pani Bottle] I wish we could go around
and do something while stalling.
[Pani Bottle coughs, clears throat]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
I played the 7,
so it should be lower than 7, right?
I think Junseo has to go against Jaegyun.
[Dail] I had to tag Yuk Junseo.
I'm going to make that happen.
[Pani Bottle] There's no way around.
Because the reeds are so...
-All five of them are there?
-Yes.
-All five of them?
-I'm not sure.
Yang Dail's missing.
[Dail] There were a lot of branches.
If I dash out making some rustling noise,
they'll have enough time to get away.
I decided to go without my shoes.
But Horseking... Right, he took the 7.
How does Eunsil take the 7?
If he won with the King,
-we can't take the 7.
-Right.
Jimin.
What?
[Joonsu] Should I just tag you?
Should I just tag you?
-[Dail] Tag.
-[grunts]
-[Jimin] Hey!
-Oh, my gosh.
[exclaims] What?
[sighs frustratedly]
-Are you okay?
-[alarm blaring]
-I'm okay.
[host] Tag confirmed.
[Horseking] Did he do it?
YANG DAIL TAGS YUK JUNSEO
[ZZONE yells] That was awesome!
-He was doing a heads-up play.
-Yeah.
-That's why he was so quiet.
-[Horseking] He was.
BLUE TEAM TAGS JUNSEO AS PLANNED
[Dail] I was being stealthy.
-I even took off my shoes...
-I see.
-...to not make any noise.
-[chuckles]
[Junseo] He even took his shoes off
and ran over.
I guess that's why
I couldn't hear him coming.
I was caught off guard.
I can't believe I got tagged.
It hurt my pride a bit.
DAIL SUBMITS AN 8
JUNSEO HANDS IN A CARD
[dealer] We will announce the results.
Yuk Junseo has won.
[♪ intense music playing]
[Dail exclaims]
-There's no need to check ours.
-[Junseo] Right.
For now, with the 8 and 9,
you should play aggressively, Junseo.
-Okay.
-Pretend to be the King.
I'll take this first.
If Yang Dail came running at me,
I'd be sure that he had a high number.
So I chose my 9
and took Dail's 8.
DAIL'S 8 GOES TO JUNSEO
-Dail had an 8.
-Right.
You got that with your 9?
Nice. So damn nice.
Yang Dail's a God damn chump now.
[Junseo] I was thankful
that he came after me.
It was amazing. I was cheering inside.
Are you okay, Dail?
No, I'm not.
-[Jaegyun] Did you fall?
-[Horseking] He fell.
-[Jaegyun] What?
-Really?
[Joonsu] You fell?
First of all, we lost.
I told you Junseo seemed
to have an 8 and 9.
It was an 8 and 9.
[sighs heavily]
I told you. He had an 8 and a 9,
so he got you with his 8
and me with his 9.
For them, that was pretty much
the best-case scenario.
They took out a high card
with another high card.
Whoa, something is seriously going wrong.
Junseo has an 8 and 3.
Horseking can tag him when he sees him.
Our 8 is gone.
[exclaims in annoyance]
[winces]
[hisses, groans]
[Dail] That hurts.
[cries out]
-[all exclaim]
-[Jaegyun] What happened?
What is it?
-Oh, no.
-[exclaims]
YANG DAIL GOT INJURED AS WELL
[♪ unsettling music playing]
Was it because I ran barefoot?
-Barefoot?
-[Joonsu] You were barefoot?
-Barefoot? With no socks?
-[Joonsu] Why?
-Shoes would make noise.
-[Horseking] To not make noise?
[Dail] I snuck in through the window.
[ZZONE] I was a bit shaken for a moment.
[Joonsu] He can't run anymore.
We're in trouble.
Could you get the medic, please?
SAFETY PRECAUTIONS WERE TAKEN
AS THE CAST MEMBER RECEIVED
PROPER FIRST AID AND CARE AFTER THE INJURY
[Horseking] The sun's setting.
8 HOURS HAVE PASSED
[Pani Bottle] This could go on all night.
THE SUN HAS SET NOW
I hope they come here. If we look...
I don't think they'll come here,
because they're scared.
RED TEAM IS STILL PLANNING
They're too scared to come over here.
But in their state of mind,
they might try to barge in.
[Junseo] Then, we should hide
if they're going to come get us.
-[Jimin] That's possible.
-Let's not go out.
RED TEAM PLANS AN AMBUSH
So the plan is to hide on the main road?
-[Junseo] Yes.
-No, you shouldn't hide.
You should stand in the front.
I was a little mad at that point.
Ddolddol was supposed to tag them
as much as possible.
But he didn't.
Whether he didn't want to or couldn't,
but he didn't. He couldn't do it.
DIDN'T PROTECT THEM FROM BEING TAGGED
[Jimin] Joonsu.
[Eunsil] Ddolddol wasn't doing his job
as the King.
DDOLDDOL RAN AWAY FIRST
[sighs]
-I think Ddolddol...
-[Ddolddol] And right now--
...can go out a bit more.
[Junseo] Horseking might barge in.
[Jimin] Ddolddol
should be the one stopping him.
[Eunsil] Do it, or change your name
to Kim Wuss-wuss.
[players laugh]
It's time for you to step up.
MEANWHILE, BLUE TEAM
[Dail] Hey, we have to win.
-[Horseking] We'll win for you. Just wait.
-Yeah. Please.
If we end up losing like this,
I'll be really pissed off.
We can win.
Right now, we know what Junseo has.
-[Joonsu] Yes.
-An 8 and 3, right?
An 8 and 3.
And Ddolddol is...
-King.
-[Dail] King.
HORSEKING LEADS BLUE TEAM MEETING
I don't think this is important.
Anyway, that's that.
-Who's next?
-Jimin, Pani Bottle, Eunsil.
-[Horseking] Jimin and?
-Pani Bottle and Eunsil.
Best case is if Junseo tags Joonsu,
and Joonsu plays a 4.
-It doesn't matter if he plays an 8.
-[Jaegyun] The best case.
-He'd never play that.
-The best-case scenario
is Joonsu tagging Junseo.
-[Joonsu] Right.
-[Dail] I think Joonsu...
[Joonsu] Our plan at this point
was to take everyone out except Ddolddol.
Since I had the most cards,
I'd take away one of Junseo's cards.
Then, the players with lower cards
would tag the other team
and give them their low cards,
while players with high cards
would wipe out those
with the low cards they planted.
We were going to make sure
we took them down with us.
-[alarm blaring]
-[host] The Battle Round has begun.
[ZZONE] Let's do this!
[Horseking] Let's go!
[Jaegyun and ZZONE] Let's go!
[exhales] Let's do this.
BLUE TEAM SPLITS UP AND CHARGES IN
[Joonsu] First, Junseo.
Yeah. Just go and get involved
with anyone, okay?
JOONSU AND DAIL PLAN TO PASS LOW CARDS
I should get tagged, right?
-By Junseo?
-Yes.
If Ddolddol is there, we have to retreat.
Yeah, that's right.
RED TEAM BASE
-[Pani Bottle] They're not here?
-I think they'll go
-around the back through the reeds.
-No, no.
They're here.
[Pani Bottle] They are?
-[Joonsu] There are three here.
-[Horseking] Three here!
[Joonsu] Pani Bottle.
Who is it?
I can only see Pani Bottle right now.
The short one.
Ddolddol needs to be in front.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[Horseking] Is it three? Who are they?
[Joonsu] Ddolddol, Jimin, and Junseo.
[Jimin] Is that Joonsu?
[Junseo] It's Joonsu.
Joonsu and Horseking.
There are three here!
-[Jimin] Joonsu and Horseking.
-[Ddolddol] Really?
[Jimin] Joonsu and Horseking.
RED TEAM STICKS TO THE PLAN
AND EVERYONE EXCEPT DDOLDDOL RUNS
LOOKING AROUND
[Horseking] My goodness.
-You don't want to go back, do you?
-[Horseking] Yeah.
[both laughing]
[Ddolddol] If I catch you, you're dead.
[Horseking] No, we won't die.
[Joonsu] As long as it's not Ddolddol,
it would be a gain, no matter who tags me.
The best option was to tag Junseo.
So, while Horseking
was distracting Ddolddol,
I was focused on finding Junseo.
[Jimin] Who's that?
[Junseo] Joonsu.
[grunts]
-[Joonsu] Are you okay?
-Tag!
LEE JOONSU TAGS YUK JUNSEO
[host] Tag confirmed.
[Junseo sighs]
TAGGED AS BLUE TEAM PLANNED
[Joonsu] I tagged Junseo as we planned,
so we got the job done.
[doorknob clicks]
I didn't have to think.
I just put down a card as we planned.
[Joonsu exhales]
YUK JUNSEO'S CARDS
[Junseo] I was very flustered.
We didn't know
the other number card Joonsu had.
THE CARD JOONSU SUBMITTED
Maybe Joonsu's planning
to use his 2 as a sacrifice.
Joonsu might dump his 2 here.
-Right.
-Then, it's best to win with the 3.
Joonsu tagged you
-knowing that you have an 8.
-[Junseo] Yes.
Then, it's a sacrifice.
That's a sacrifice play.
RED TEAM EXPECTS JOONSU TO PLAY A 2
YUK JUNSEO'S CARDS
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
LEE JOONSU, YUK JUNSEO
[dealer] Lee Joonsu...
has won.
BLUE TEAM BRINGS JUNSEO
DOWN TO A SINGLE CARD
Yeah! I beat Junseo.
[chuckling]
[cheering]
Well done, well done.
-It was a 3.
-[Horseking] What?
The 3 card.
-[Horseking] Nice! I knew it!
-[Jaegyun] Nice!
[Horseking] Okay!
Then, the 3 card! Hold on.
-You brought the 3?
-[Joonsu] Yes.
-[Jaegyun] He did. Good.
-[Joonsu] I did.
-[Horseking] Crushed it. Just one left.
-[Jaegyun] Just one left.
JUNSEO IS DOWN TO AN 8
-Now then...
-Let's go.
I can go tag any of those four.
[Horseking] Right, since you have a 2,
it's your turn to step in.
[sighs]
I played a 3 and lost.
-You lost?
-[Junseo] Yes.
[Pani Bottle] He had a stronger card.
[sighs heavily]
[Ddolddol] They'll now try
to eliminate Junseo.
-Then, he has a 2 and 3 now?
-Yes.
I think that's okay though.
That seems okay.
Now, he has a 2 and 3.
Then, I can beat that.
I can beat Joonsu for sure.
You can beat Joonsu for sure.
You can tag Dail or Joonsu.
-I can get him.
-[Ddolddol] Yeah.
Then, I'm better off doing it
since I have a 5.
-[Jimin] Yes. It's the same.
-It's the same.
I thought about it and realized
that with Junseo's 3 gone,
Joonsu was guaranteed to have the 2 and 3.
We'd seen all of Joonsu's cards now.
We could take him out for sure,
so our target became Lee Joonsu.
WITH HIS CARDS KNOWN,
JOONSU BECOMES THE TARGET
Joonsu will get involved again.
They'll come together.
[Pani Bottle] If you see Joonsu near me
when I'm hiding,
-go after him.
-[alarm blaring]
Go for him! Go, go!
[host] The Battle Round has begun.
[♪ thrilling music playing]
[Pani Bottle coughs]
RED TEAM PLANS TO AMBUSH JOONSU
KIM DDOLDDOL IS OFF TO GET HORSEKING
-[Ddolddol] Who are they?
-[Jimin] Horseking, Joonsu!
[Ddolddol] Horseking and Joonsu!
[Pani Bottle] Is Joonsu here?
-[Jimin] Joonsu.
-Is he with Horseking?
[sighs] It feels like Horseking
will lose Ddolddol and run like hell.
-Be careful.
-[Ddolddol] How about heading back?
It's pointless to tag each other.
-[Ddolddol] That's true.
-Yes.
[♪ thrilling music intensifies]
[Jimin] Joonsu's coming!
-Why are you coming?
-[Joonsu] What?
-[Pani Bottle] Be careful.
-[alarm blaring]
PANI BOTTLE TAGS JOONSU
[host] Tag confirmed.
PANI BOTTLE
[Joonsu] This is mine.
[dealer] Pani Bottle has won.
[Pani Bottle] Okay.
He played a 3, and I won.
-[Ddolddol] Nice.
-[Jimin] We won.
-You played your 5?
-Yes.
-[Ddolddol] No way.
-Then, he must have a 2.
-Yeah, a 2.
-Right.
-[Jimin] Tag him.
-[Pani Bottle] We have to go for Joonsu.
-[Junseo] Yeah.
-[Pani Bottle] The best move
is to put all focus on Joonsu
and eliminate him first.
If we eliminate Joonsu this time,
we'll have a huge advantage.
So when I start, I'll run like hell,
hide, and go after Joonsu. Okay?
-[Ddolddol] Yes.
-Sounds good.
-[alarm blaring]
-[host] The Battle Round has begun.
[Ddolddol] It's Horseking and Joonsu.
It's the same as before.
SAME STAND-OFF AS BEFORE
-Go!
-[Ddolddol] Wait, timeout! [laughs]
Timeout.
[Horseking] It's okay! Go!
[Ddolddol] Timeout. Hey, Joonsu's coming!
[Horseking] Okay, be careful!
JIMIN WAITING TO AMBUSH
[Joonsu grunts]
-[Jimin] I got you! Tag!
-[alarm blaring]
[host] Tag confirmed.
I don't have any other card now.
PARK JIMIN, LEE JOONSU
There's no need to think.
[panting]
RED TEAM SUCCEEDS IN DEFEATING JOONSU
I won.
-A 2?
-[Jimin] Yeah, 2.
-You beat a 2 with the 6?
-What?
You beat a 2 with the 6?
-I--
-[Ddolddol] Then Joonsu's out, right?
-He's out.
-[Ddolddol] Nice.
How about we get more aggressive?
-Wait, do they tell us when someone's out?
-Yes.
Yeah, ZZONE--
Yet he survived?
-They let us know?
-Yes, when someone's out.
[Ddolddol] They'd let us know.
-He could have the Joker.
-[gasps]
-Out...
-[Jimin] What if...
THE PLAYER WITH THE JOKER
HAS THREE CARDS
Joonsu is the Joker?
-Joonsu is the Joker?
-[Pani Bottle] The Joker?
Joker? He's the Joker?
Is that possible?
If the alarm goes off now, he's the Joker.
Fuck.
[alarm blaring]
So...
He is! He's the Joker!
The Joker for Joonsu?
Yes, we can't change it now.
-This should be our cheat code.
-[ZZONE] I bet they won't expect this.
JOKER
[Jaegyun] Let's give it to Joonsu,
the last person they'd expect.
[ZZONE] Then, Joonsu has 9, 4,
and the Joker.
LEE JOONSU, JOKER
[ZZONE and Dail sigh]
That was a mistake. Jimin got 2,
and they found out Joonsu is the Joker.
What a headache.
I should've gone with him.
-[ZZONE sniffles]
-[sighs]
I really panicked at that moment.
-The Joker was a little too bold.
-They pulled a fast one on us.
They've been bluffing
in front of us big time.
-It began with that notebook.
-[Jimin] Yeah.
-The King was pointless?
-Yeah.
Their Joker only has one card,
so he's actually more vulnerable.
We've figured out their Joker,
while they have no idea about our Joker.
If we get Joonsu, that's huge.
If I get Joonsu,
the game is basically over.
-[Jimin] Right.
-Yeah.
RED TEAM GAINS UPPER HAND
BY FINDING OUT THE OTHER JOKER
[Joonsu] So, if I get tagged by Ddolddol,
it's basically over for us.
-It's over.
-Nothing would beat the King.
[Joonsu] Then, how do we win?
-We have to get their Joker.
-[ZZONE] Yes.
THEY COULD LOSE THEIR JOKER
-Anyway, we don't know their Joker?
-[Jaegyun] We don't.
These three might have the Joker,
but we have to tag them.
-[Dail] Right.
-[Horseking] Yes.
[Jaegyun] We need to eliminate
at least one of them.
-Right. Right.
-[Jaegyun] We need to isolate them.
That's how we'll know,
but we haven't eliminated anyone.
Let's go together this time.
[alarm blaring]
[host] The Battle Round has begun.
JOONSU RUSHES OUT
AS SOON AS THE ROUND STARTS
[Joonsu] I ran over to the reeds
as soon as we started.
[gasps] I can see the stars.
They figured out that I was the Joker.
-[Jaegyun] Stay hidden.
-I'll hide.
-You keep hiding.
-[Jaegyun] Keep hiding.
-Stay in the reeds.
[Joonsu] I said "Okay" and hid.
I just stayed there quietly.
Until we figure out who the Joker is,
we need to play it very safe.
Hey, Boss.
-[Ddolddol laughs] Why are you alone?
-Why not?
-[Ddolddol] They must have gone off.
-Yes, I just need to wait.
KIM DDOLDDOL BLOCKS HORSEKING
-I want to go in.
-No, Horseking.
-[Horseking] I know.
-Don't cross this line.
-You can't.
-[Horseking] I know. I totally understand.
[♪ light music playing]
BLUE TEAM HAS TO ELIMINATE SOMEONE
[Jaegyun] Not here.
No one's here.
RED TEAM IS NOWHERE TO BE FOUND
[Dail] Geez, I can't believe this.
[Eunsil whispers] Jimin.
ZZONE and Jaegyun are waiting down there.
They're in front of the door.
They're at the door.
UPDATING JUNSEO
ZZONE.
-[Jimin] Once they come upstairs...
-[Eunsil] I'll tag them.
[Ddolddol] It seems like
one person's missing.
There should be four of them there.
-Tag.
-[host] Tag confirmed.
KIM DDOLDDOL TAGS HORSEKING
A TIE BETWEEN KINGS
-Come on.
-[Horseking] Let me inside.
-[Ddolddol] No.
-[Horseking sighs]
[Horseking] Did you get training?
You're pretty good at defense.
[Ddolddol] No, nothing like that.
I've got so much to do though.
I need to get rid of Jimin
and Pani Bottle.
[Ddolddol laughing] Tag!
-[host] Tag confirmed.
-[Ddolddol] Stay away.
They're not coming.
DDOLDDOL'S SECOND SUCCESSFUL DEFENSE
How long are you going to do this?
[Ddolddol] Beats me.
[Horseking] This is driving me crazy.
Am I the one who's bad at this?
KIM DDOLDDOL'S IMPENETRABLE DEFENSE
10 HOURS HAVE PASSED
[Jaegyun] They're all hiding
and won't come out.
[ZZONE sighs] Where could they be?
They were hiding and refusing to come out.
Time was ticking.
HELPLESS AGAINST RED TEAM'S DEFENSE
All they did was play defense.
There was nothing we could do.
I felt so frustrated.
[Dail] I can't believe we've been playing
the game for 10 hours.
Only Ddolddol's walking around.
The other four are all hiding.
[exhales heavily]
They're not going to move at all?
-They know they have the upper hand.
-Of course.
They're not coming out.
They're now lying on the pitch
and not getting up.
It made me mad and worked up.
-We need to find symbols.
-[Jaegyun] Yes, we should.
Right, no matter what.
-Just force them to crawl out?
-[Dail] Yes.
So we smoke them
out of their little hideout?
Wait them out? Okay, got it.
We decided to find all 10 symbols.
Fine, no one's coming out from the base.
We might as well find the symbols
and get rid of them.
Let's lay out rat poison
and wait them out.
I started feeling more determined.
We have to win this.
This place is so narrow.
You practically picked a fortress.
It's a fortress.
You're like Zhang Fei at Changban Bridge.
[chuckles] This is driving me nuts.
It's pointless between us.
So let's wait until they tag each other.
[ZZONE whispering] Jaegyun.
Be really careful.
[Jaegyun] Are they on this side?
This side?
-[ZZONE] Isn't this the Neutral Zone?
-[Jaegyun] Right.
Let's find them.
[ZZONE] It feels like they'll be here.
RED TEAM BASE, 1ST FLOOR
RED TEAM BASE, 2ND FLOOR
RED TEAM IS STILL HIDING
ON THE 2ND FLOOR
[Jaegyun pants]
Why aren't they here?
[object thuds]
-[Ddolddol] Someone's hiding back there.
-[laughs smugly]
Who could that be?
Don't look.
WHILE HORSEKING DISTRACTS DDOLDDOL
[exhales] I just need to find one.
I wanted to find a symbol so badly.
It was so hard to find.
Time kept ticking away.
I was getting more and more desperate.
[Jimin] Eunsil.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[Eunsil whispers] They're inside.
[object clangs]
They're rummaging around.
[hinges creak]
[Jimin whispers] We need to catch the one
who'll sacrifice themselves.
[sighs]
[Eunsil] Want to go to the second floor?
[♪ epic music playing]
[Jaegyun] There it was.
That feeling I felt then
was something
I really can't put into words.
I wanted to shout, but if I did,
the other team would come.
I celebrated on the inside
and took it with me.
I ran so fast like my ass was on fire.
The fourth one.
BLUE TEAM TAKES FOURTH SYMBOL
-Wait, what's this?
-[Ddolddol] Stop lying.
"Blue Team retrieved the fourth symbol."
"Red Team's 8 card
is held by Yuk Junseo." Nice!
Okay!
When it was broken, the 8 was revealed
according to the 4 card rule.
Didn't they say if we broke four,
we'd know who had the 4?
Yeah, so if there's no 4,
it goes to 5, then 6, then 7, and then 8.
-That means 4, 5, 6, 7 are gone.
-Right.
[Jaegyun] Let's run
through the possibilities.
[Horseking] From 1 to 9, there's no 9.
-[Jaegyun] It's an 8.
-They don't have these.
-[Jaegyun] No, they don't.
-Then, it's 1, 2, 3, and 8.
[Jaegyun] Yeah, he's got an 8.
[Horseking] The only combinations
are 1, 2, and 3.
Eunsil has the 1!
[panting]
-We got it. It's a 1.
-[Horseking] It's over.
THE MYSTERY BEHIND THE 1 AND 3 CARDS
WHICH ONE IS EUNSIL'S CARD?
I have the 1 and 7 cards.
It's confirmed. Eunsil has a 1.
BLUE TEAM CORRECTLY MATCHES
EUNSIL'S CARD
Ddolddol is the one with 3.
I'll take the King and 3.
KIM DDOLDDOL'S CARDS
-Ddolddol has the 3.
-Yes. And Eunsil has the 1.
GETS DDOLDDOL'S CARD RIGHT TOO
[Dail] It was super helpful.
It's the incredible power
of the 4 card rule.
[Pani Bottle]
Then, the 1 has been revealed.
-[Ddolddol] They know all our cards now.
-Right.
[Pani Bottle sighs] Then, what do we do?
[sighs heavily]
[exhales]
We're sticking with the same strategy.
Tag either Jaegyun or Joonsu.
If we manage to take their Joker,
then until the game's over,
-just stay hidden forever.
-I can do that.
The Joker can change with three more,
so they'll come for sure.
CAN SHUFFLE CARDS
AFTER RETRIEVING 7 SYMBOLS
We'd just need to wait.
THEY FIGURE BLUE TEAM
WILL COME TO RETRIEVE SYMBOLS
Hey, let's do it with style.
[Dail] Okay.
-And get Junseo. Go out in style.
-Yeah. With style.
I'll just charge at whoever I see.
If I replace Junseo's 8 with my 1,
Horseking won't have any numbers
that can threaten him.
He'll be free to move around.
If you just take Junseo down
and lower his number,
no matter if this person, this person,
or this person has the Joker,
they're all done for if I use my 5.
[Jaegyun] The 5 can beat anyone.
They'll be done for.
And we can just go straight in.
As the King, I absolutely needed a card
with a higher number than their Joker.
If their Joker's other number card
is greater than mine,
they would play it, beat mine,
and take my number.
Then, I'd be left with only the King
and no way to defend myself.
On the other hand,
if their Joker's number card
is lower than mine,
I can defend myself with my number card
regardless of what the Joker plays.
[Dail] Hey, this time,
let's stay calm and get this done.
Dail has to endure so much.
-Seriously.
-Not at all.
-[ZZONE] How bad is it?
-It feels like it burst again.
Even if my toe falls off,
I can't let the game end like this.
I'll see this game through to the end.
So that's why
both sides decided to go
with the sacrifice play.
[alarm blaring]
[host] The Battle Round has begun.
12 HOURS HAVE PASSED
NO ONE'S COMING TO RED TEAM BASE
[object rustling]
[♪ intriguing music playing]
[whispering] Are they inside?
No, no one's here.
-You haven't seen Joonsu, right?
-No, he's not here.
[Junseo] Blue Team didn't come this time.
-Did they come in at all?
-Nope.
[sighs] What's going on?
Some of them are coming. Yang Dail and...
-Four of them.
-[Pani Bottle] Who?
[Eunsil] Yang Dail and ZZONE.
Dail is limping.
BLUE TEAM SEEN IN FRONT OF THE REEDS
Are they going to the right?
What do we do?
[Jimin] They suddenly went into the reeds
to look for symbols, so it was weird.
[Horseking groans] Geez.
Please, just let one show up.
[ZZONE] Please.
BLUE TEAM SEARCHES THE REEDS FOR SYMBOLS
[Horseking] Be careful not to step on it.
[ZZONE] Okay.
[Jimin sighs] It's really hard
to tag someone if they go in there.
[Eunsil] I know.
It feels like we have to do something now.
[Jimin] Horseking went in there
to look for symbols.
-Three of them are searching.
-How about we all go into their base?
-All of us?
-[Jimin] Yes.
I think we can sneak around from behind.
They're all focused on that.
-And Joonsu could be alone at the base.
-[♪ rock music playing]
But we have to move quickly.
Let's make the first move.
It's better than having them wait us out.
They're all in the reeds anyway.
-[Ddolddol] Yes.
-[Horseking] It'll take time for Horseking
to crawl out of the reeds.
Now's our chance while they're distracted.
BLUE TEAM'S FOCUSED ON FINDING SYMBOLS
[Junseo] Ddolddol, you go forward.
[Jimin] I think we should head this way.
-I'll search.
-You should go that way.
[Dail] There they are!
RED TEAM SPOTTED
-[Horseking] Okay. Who is it?
-All of them are here!
-They're all coming.
-They're all here.
Get ready!
THE BLUE TEAM COMES OUT ON CUE
[groans] The Red Team
had stubbornly done nothing
but defend and hole up in their fortress,
so our plan was to lure them out.
[sighs]
We're in trouble.
Here they come.
Run.
We have to run.
[Jimin] We can't be caught by Yang Dail.
-Yang Dail's coming.
-We can't let him tag us.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[Dail panting]
I figured that was my moment.
I was like, "Guys,
I'm going in."
"Yang Sacrifice is going in. This is it."
I was ready to sacrifice myself
for the team.
[Jimin] Junseo.
[screams] Wait, no!
-[alarm blaring]
-[host] Tag confirmed.
[Horseking] Wait, what?
What happened?
[♪ intriguing music playing]
-I guess it was a dogfight.
-[Horseking] Yeah. What happened?
[panting]
[Dail] My goodness.
[♪ powerful music playing]
Yuk Junseo!
YANG DAIL TAGS YUK JUNSEO
-This is insane.
-[Horseking] Yang Dail, Yuk Junseo!
[chuckles]
-Yang Dail! General Yang!
-[ZZONE laughing]
Despite being injured,
Dail managed to tag Junseo.
It was a play that went beyond
what he was physically capable of.
It's like the goalkeeper went and scored.
[Junseo] It was
right before Jimin got tagged.
Junseo, you get him.
[Junseo] She was calling out
because if she got caught again,
the Joker would be revealed.
I rushed forward and grabbed him.
[Dail] I was going to tag Yuk Junseo.
Suddenly, he was protecting Jimin.
I tagged him, saying, "Well, thanks."
So, we went there and...
Gosh, here's mine.
I switched it to my 1 in the card battle.
YANG DAIL, YUK JUNSEO
[host] Yang Dail has been eliminated.
[all cheering]
[Horseking] Nice.
[Dail] I've done my part for today.
[host] Yang Dail has been eliminated.
[Jimin sighs]
-Good work, Junseo.
-Thanks.
-[Jimin] What card is it?
-A 1.
-A 1?
-Yes, we need to make a move now.
-Was it a 1?
-[Eunsil] Yang Dail had a 1.
[Junseo] Mine became a 1.
My 8 has changed to a 1.
Not a 2, but a 1.
He pulled off the damn sacrifice play.
Shit, I should've caught him.
-I should've been tagged.
-[Junseo] Why?
You know I have a 2.
[sighs in disappointment]
Now what do we do?
[Pani Bottle] This one hurt a lot.
It was a big blow.
[Eunsil] I was so frustrated.
[Horseking] ♪ Ready or not, here I come ♪
-They should be hiding.
-What?
-I think they're hiding.
-Yeah, let's search this side.
THE KING AND 5 COME CHARGING IN AGAIN
♪ Ready or not, here I come ♪
Is he alone? It sounds like he's alone.
Who's there?
HORSEKING WALKS AROUND FREELY
Is he alone?
THE RED TEAM HAS NO WAY TO STOP HIM
Is he by himself?
After that,
our morale really took a big hit.
Yes, it wasn't easy at all.
It was hard to keep it together.
The Blue Team kept pressing us.
-[Jimin grunts] Hold on.
-[Jaegyun] Tag.
[Eunsil and Jaegyun] Tag!
-[alarm blaring]
-[host] Tag confirmed.
Jang Eunsil has been eliminated.
-Now, ZZONE.
-[ZZONE] Yes?
-You go there like earlier.
-[ZZONE] I'll bring it over this time.
Bring it over, and we'll swap.
We'll win for sure.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
I'm out of it right now.
I can't think properly.
[ZZONE] Here.
[Jaegyun]
Give us the Shuffle Ticket, please.
Let's go, ZZONE.
[ZZONE] Shall we go switch right now?
ZZONE had a 6 left,
so we decided to use a Shuffle Ticket.
I'd switch with ZZONE
and use my 6 to take them down.
-[dealer] The Shuffle Ticket will be used.
-[ZZONE] Okay.
[host] The Blue Team has used
their Shuffle Ticket.
THE RED TEAM IS HELPLESS
[Jimin] Horseking and a 1 card.
We got a message.
What is it?
WITH 7 SYMBOLS,
BLUE TEAM EARNS SHUFFLE TICKET
-They've retrieved seven symbols.
-[Ddolddol] A Shuffle Ticket?
[groans] Jaegyun got it.
The big card from ZZONE.
Is it a Joker?
They've been searching.
-Seven of them.
-[Pani Bottle] Right.
It's not a good idea to ignore searching.
Should we make a guess?
Maybe Joonsu now has a 6.
And ZZONE has the Joker?
-[Ddolddol] He must've passed the Joker.
-[Jimin] No.
I think ZZONE and Jaegyun would switch.
[Ddolddol] That will be it, 'cause Jaegyun
will come running toward us
with a 6 or 5.
[Pani Bottle] Jaegyun must've gotten a 6.
ZZONE has the 1, and Joonsu has the Joker.
So we definitely have to make our move.
It was like everything
that could go wrong went wrong.
It felt like all the bad luck
hit our team at once.
[sighs]
But Horseking...
Horseking...
We should go after Horseking. [sniffles]
It doesn't matter
who's tagged by Horseking.
Just like how we didn't know
that Joonsu was the Joker,
they can't rule anyone out.
If Horseking has a regular card,
he'll probably play it safe
if he still has it.
And he'd play that first.
-[Ddolddol] So, we have to be tagged.
-Yeah.
[Ddolddol] They're going to think,
"Why do they keep protecting Junseo?"
I don't think they've ruled him out
as the Joker yet.
They'll definitely assume
he'll play the Joker.
I think they'll suspect he's the Joker.
Normally, they'd expect Junseo to say,
"Let's do two-on-two."
[Jimin] Yes.
But if he doesn't come out
because of injury,
they might assume the Joker was hurt.
-They'll think they have the upper hand.
-[Jimin] Right.
Horseking probably thinks,
"Junseo's got something up his sleeves."
Because Junseo's been playing
very aggressively.
I think they're convinced
I'm holding the Joker.
Let's just tag Horseking.
This could actually be
a game-changing move.
If I get caught, Horseking will expect me
to play the Joker.
-Yes.
-But I have to play the 1.
[Pani Bottle] He ends up
with the King and a 1.
-Right.
-Yes.
If he has the King and a 1,
she will have a decent shot against him.
[Pani Bottle] Now,
it's totally just a battle of wits.
So, it has to be King and 1.
I'll try to catch him.
PLAN TO LOWER
HORSEKING'S REGULAR CARD TO A 1
Once I got a 1,
it felt like I had nothing to lose.
Our remaining numbers were really low.
But one thing gave us hope.
They didn't know who our Joker was.
So we figured
we should just attack the King.
[Horseking] They'll probably do everything
they can to keep Joker hidden.
Whether it's Pani Bottle or Jimin,
they'll keep it hidden.
Their focus should be hiding
the identity of the Joker.
We still don't know who the Joker is.
We don't know what's going to happen.
Once we identify the Joker,
they're done for.
[ZZONE] How are we going
to get rid of Ddolddol's 3?
-[Jaegyun] We'll find three more symbols.
-[ZZONE] Okay.
Once Ddolddol's 3 disappears,
-they're left with one King.
-Yes. Ddolddol's card will be gone.
The highest card they had was only a 3.
I had a 5.
As long as Junseo
doesn't tag me with his 1
and I tag Jimin or Pani Bottle,
the game is over.
[alarm blaring]
We just need to corner them.
We're on the offensive.
[Jaegyun] If we go at them, they'll panic.
I'll go right. You two go left.
Horseking, let me know
-if four of them come.
-[Horseking] Sure.
[Pani Bottle] Let's just check
where Horseking is.
RED TEAM'S TARGET IS HORSEKING
[Ddolddol] I don't think they will try
to sneak in anymore.
[Pani Bottle] Let me know
if you see anyone.
[Ddolddol] He's coming.
-[Pani Bottle] Is someone there?
-Yes.
[Pani Bottle] Then, I'll go around.
-I'll go around.
-[Junseo] Yes, go ahead.
BLUE TEAM MEMBERS ENTER
FROM DIFFERENT DIRECTIONS
-[Jimin] Is that Horseking up ahead?
-[Junseo] Yes.
-[Jimin] He's alone.
-[Junseo] Right.
[Jimin] How about the three of us
charge him?
-[Junseo] Sure, I'll tag him.
-[Jimin] I won't tag him.
There are three here! Kim Ddolddol.
-Junseo!
-[Jaegyun] What?
[Horseking] Pani Bottle is hiding!
No one's here.
PANI BOTTLE SPOTTED JAEGYUN AND JOONSU
[Pani Bottle] Jaegyun's on this side.
-There are four here!
-Jaegyun's on that side.
Jaegyun's over there.
[Horseking] Four!
Four people are coming!
HORSEKING IS OUTNUMBERED 4 TO 1
Come this way! We can surround them!
-[Jaegyun] What?
-[Joonsu] I can't hear him.
[Jaegyun] Horseking, what did you say?
JAEGYUN AND JOONSU ARE PANICKING
[Pani Bottle] Cover my back.
RED TEAM HUNTS HORSEKING
[Horseking] Coming our way!
The plan was to avoid getting caught
by Junseo and have our team members
surround and tag them.
[sighs]
But it didn't go as planned.
[Junseo] You can come with us.
Stick with us.
[Pani Bottle] Okay.
No one's here.
JAEGYUN AND JOONSU
ARE UNAWARE OF HORSEKING'S SITUATION
HORSEKING IS COMPLETELY CORNERED
Let's give it a shot.
YUK JUNSEO CHARGES IN
HORSEKING PANICS
[♪ tense music playing]
JUNSEO TAGS HORSEKING
-[Junseo] Okay.
-[alarm blaring]
[Horseking] Okay, okay.
[host] Tag confirmed.
So fast.
[Jimin] Junseo's still got it.
Ah, I may have exposed
my play style too much.
My plan to escape
using parkour didn't work.
[dealer] Horseking, Yuk Junseo,
please submit your cards.
[♪ intriguing music playing]
[Junseo] I had to get
inside the King's head.
They'd basically had the game in the bag,
but there was a small chance
it could all suddenly slip away.
[Horseking] We haven't figured out
who's holding the Joker yet.
If Junseo has the Joker
and decides to play the Joker
instead of a number card,
I could be the one who loses.
This is Horseking's.
[dealer] We will check the cards.
YUK JUNSEO, HORSEKING
Horseking has won.
[Horseking] Unfortunately, I had no choice
but to play the 5.
I made the best choice I could at the time
and I think it paid off.
[host] Yuk Junseo is eliminated.
JANG EUNSIL, YUK JUNSEO, YANG DAIL
ELIMINATED
[ZZONE groans] This is insane.
It wasn't Eunsil or Junseo?
THE JOKER SUSPECTS ARE DOWN TO TWO
What a shame.
Maybe I should've battled them.
-[Joonsu] But four-on-one was too much.
-[Jaegyun] Yeah.
KING UNFORTUNATELY LOST A HIGH NUMBER
[Horseking] I'm sorry.
[inhales] I made a mistake.
-We gave them hope at the last minute.
-Yes.
[sighs]
[Horseking] Yes, it was my arrogance
and a huge mistake on my part.
I basically took away
all the possible ways we could win
and gave the opposing team
a few possible ways to win.
-It was a bit of a shame at the end.
-[Horseking] I know.
HORSEKING CAN'T EASILY DEFEND HIS KING
[Jimin] Horseking must've played
a regular card, right?
Playing the King would be too risky.
He must've thought there was no way
I'd only given Junseo regular cards,
so I think Horseking played
a regular number card.
Horseking must've taken the 1 card.
Could they think I'm the Joker?
-Is that possible?
-It is.
Let's say Horseking comes to tag us.
If he plays a 1, and I play a 3,
and I'm lucky enough to take the 1,
then he'd only have the King.
Horseking has no idea
which one of us is the Joker.
If either Jimin or I get tagged,
Horseking will definitely play a 1.
Then, we could play our number cards
to get rid of his number card.
He'd be left with only the King,
giving us a clear advantage.
So we decided to go all-in
on tagging Horseking.
[groans] Those punks are all coming.
No, there are two.
We'll be at a disadvantage fighting here,
so we'll slowly draw them out.
Let's stall here, okay?
-Let's circle around in the open area.
-[Joonsu] Okay.
HORSEKING AND JOONSU FROM THE BLUE TEAM
[Horseking]
We'll definitely see an opening,
whether it's Jimin or someone else.
Let's stall here.
Go around that way.
KIM DDOLDDOL'S IRONCLAD DEFENSE
Hey, get in there
and hit them from the back.
[Pani Bottle] Horseking was our target,
but he kept coming out to face us.
The opportunity was definitely there,
but it was hard to find the right moment.
[Ddolddol] Then I will...
Hey, Joonsu's behind you.
[Pani Bottle] I'll stay here.
[Jimin] No, no.
[♪ ominous music plays]
[Jimin grunts]
[grunts softly]
[Jimin grunting]
JOKER PARK JIMIN AMBUSHES HORSEKING
FAILS TO TAG
[Horseking grunts]
[Horseking] Okay, got him. Nice!
Let's play.
HORSEKING TAGS PANI BOTTLE
-[alarm blaring]
-[host] Tag confirmed.
Why did he come at me? Why did he tag me?
The strategy did work,
but on the other hand,
since he knew I wasn't the Joker,
he might play the King or the 5,
which could make it tough for us to win.
[dealer] Pani Bottle has submitted a card.
Here is the result, Pani Bottle has won.
[Horseking] Let's go.
I was so surprised. "Really? I won?"
[Horseking sighs] For crying out loud.
Horseking was convinced I was the Joker.
He was sure I was the Joker,
so he played the 1
to try to take the Joker.
That was immense.
That was a huge miscalculation.
[Pani Bottle] What matters most
is that I'm still in the game,
and the King
has no other number cards left.
If he's up against the Joker, he's dead.
Now, he has only the King card.
-What?
-[Pani Bottle] He played the 1.
-[Ddolddol] Really?
-Yeah, no elimination announcement.
-No way.
-He only has one King left.
He played the 1, thinking I had the Joker.
-Can they not confirm it?
-I can't believe this.
[Ddolddol] Pani Bottle did an amazing job.
I'm not sure if Pani Bottle did well
or if Horseking did poorly.
He took the 1 with just a 3. [laughs]
We survived one more time.
That works in our favor
because Pani Bottle
could still pretend to be the Joker,
while Jimin was the real Joker
and I was the King.
So, for the other team,
it was difficult to be sure
about picking someone to attack,
except for Horseking.
But now he's down to just the King.
Oh my gosh, look at this.
The King has been crippled. [chuckles]
He's been stripped of his crown.
[Jaegyun] How did it go?
I'm sorry, it's because I threw away
my 5 on Junseo.
If only I played better
and took one card away,
I could've taken another card.
[sighs]
Having just the King is really risky.
The one thing that went wrong
with our strategy
was because of my mistake,
so it really hurt knowing that.
He desperately protected Jimin.
I know.
-Is it Jimin?
-Is Jimin the Joker?
[Horseking] Right?
That's what I'm really suspicious of.
We actually got into a scuffle,
and Pani Bottle
wouldn't stop protecting her.
What do we do then?
[Jaegyun] What?
BLUE TEAM STILL HAS NO CLUE
WHO THE JOKER IS
All they have is the King.
He'll be hard for you to tag, but still...
Shit, if I get him, it's really over.
They'll keep running like hell.
The best-case scenario
-would be what played out just now.
-[Jimin] Right.
-If we get another situation like that...
-[Ddolddol] Yeah.
...I can get him.
Pani Bottle has to buy me
a bit more time without getting caught.
In that situation, can I let him get me?
Wait for Horseking to let his guard down
and then tag him.
-Yeah, make yourself an easy target.
-Okay.
We really have no idea
what's going to happen.
Let's just go for it like moths to a flame
and see what happens.
[♪ thrilling music playing]
[Ddolddol] Two are coming.
It's the same two.
-[Pani Bottle] The same? Okay.
-Just like before.
-[Pani Bottle] I'll throw myself at him.
-Okay.
[Pani Bottle] It's like a final showdown.
[sighs heavily]
Enemies always end up crossing paths.
[Horseking] It's all or nothing now.
[♪ thrilling music continues playing]
This is crazy.
How did we get to this point?
We were so close to winning
a little while ago.
[Pani Bottle] Shield, move forward.
Shield, move to the front.
-Come here.
-[Ddolddol] Should we go
-all the way to their side?
-[Pani Bottle] Yes.
Let's see how long you can run from us.
-[Horseking] Come and get me.
-Walk, walk.
[Ddolddol exclaims]
RED TEAM CONFIDENTLY MARCHES FORWARD
[Pani Bottle] We thought
we had a pretty big advantage,
so we started to be more aggressive.
There are too many of you.
[Pani Bottle] This won't do.
Let's take out the Pink Princess.
-[Jimin] Pink Princess?
-[Pani Bottle] Yes.
-[Ddolddol] The Princess.
-Yeah.
-It'll be over soon.
-[Jimin] There's the Pink Princess.
Where's the Pink Princess?
There she is.
[ZZONE panting]
What is she doing?
ZZONE & JAEGYUN
COME WITH RED TEAM'S SYMBOLS
[groans]
[Horseking] Hey!
JOONSU BLOCKS THE WAY
It's okay, get up. Okay, play defense.
[ZZONE] It was so scary.
[Horseking] Play defense!
It's okay. Play defense. Go all the way.
They're all here! Hurry!
[Jaegyun] Get in there now, ZZONE.
They're in a standoff. Go!
-[clatters]
-[alarm blaring]
[host] Ten Red Team symbols
have been retrieved.
[Jaegyun] That's 10.
HIGH-CARD ELIMINATION TICKET EARNED
Everything was going exactly to our plan.
[Jaegyun] How did it go?
HORSEKING TAGS PANI BOTTLE
I'm sorry, it's because I threw away
my 5 on Junseo.
Then, you two
-stall instead of taking them on.
-Okay.
They have only three left.
-All three of them will come out.
-Yes.
I'll go around, head upstairs,
and grab a symbol.
-There are four upstairs.
-[Horseking] Okay.
JAEGYUN & ZZONE SECRETLY FOUND SYMBOLS
We could've easily lost our advantage,
so we decided to delay the tag.
If we find all 10,
their 3 card would disappear,
leaving only the King.
We changed our plan
and looked for the symbols first
while Horseking kept them busy.
-Come here.
-[Ddolddol] Should we go
-all the way to their side?
-[Pani Bottle] Yes.
Let's see how long you can run from us.
ENTERING RED TEAM BASE
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
We were dead set on winning,
no matter what it took.
We kept at it and collected all 10.
They found one, and we collected all 10.
Now, they only have the King.
They have nowhere to run.
[host] Red Team's highest number card,
Kim Ddolddol's 3 card, is out.
DDOLDDOL: KING
PANI BOTTLE: 1, JIMIN: 2, JOKER
[Pani Bottle exclaims]
We were thinking we could win
and just needed to get Horseking.
Then suddenly, the siren went off
and our 3 was gone.
They found all 10 symbols,
so I've been stripped of my crown too.
Both Kings are down
to just their own cards.
If I run into the Joker,
I'm completely screwed.
Something's seriously gone wrong.
-Did they find them all?
-[Ddolddol] Yes, 10.
So now it's a matter
of who tags who first?
WHO WILL BEAT THE OTHER KING FIRST?
-[Horseking] We're almost there.
-Almost there.
-[Horseking] The four of us can do this.
-[Jaegyun] Good job stalling.
From now on, they're going to...
-[Jaegyun] They'll protect him.
-...protect Ddolddol.
-Right.
-We could let the Joker
walk around out in the open.
We can surround him,
lure him in, and tag him,
but here's the thing.
I'm in a situation where I have to run.
-[Jaegyun] Right.
-Because of the Joker.
So you have to keep an eye on Jimin.
-[Jaegyun] Yeah.
-Right.
I think Jimin is the Joker.
[Jimin] Should I take on Horseking?
I don't think I can tag Horseking easily.
As long as we get one of them, we're good.
-Among Joonsu, ZZONE, and Jaegyun.
-Yes.
[Pani Bottle]
Instead of chasing Horseking,
we should find ZZONE and tag her.
Our plan for the second half was simple.
From here on out,
just go all in and tag them.
Like a moth to a flame.
Each of us had a role.
My role was to tag someone
with a regular number and eliminate them.
Jimin's job was to somehow tag Horseking.
Pani Bottle's role
was to take away the Joker.
That was our plan.
-I'll run the moment I see them.
-[Jimin] Let's go.
[Ddolddol] I'll do my best
to tag ZZONE, no matter what.
[Jimin] Okay.
-[ZZONE sighs] This is crazy.
-Just one more time.
We're almost there. [exhales]
-[sighs]
-We're really grinding them down.
-[ZZONE] Yes, we're wearing them down.
-[Jaegyun] Exactly.
We've pulled those who were hiding out.
[alarm blaring]
-Let's go slow.
-[Horseking] Go slow.
-[Joonsu] Okay.
-[ZZONE] Let's keep up the momentum.
[host] The Battle Round has begun.
We've got them cornered now.
But one wrong tag, and it's over.
-I know, we're so close.
-Yeah, we have them backed into a corner.
We're like moths to a flame right now.
-I know.
-[laughing]
[Ddolddol] It's all about momentum.
Don't get scared.
-All four of them are here.
-[Jimin] They're all here.
[sighs] Seriously...
[Horseking] Everyone
knows their target, right?
-[ZZONE] Yes.
-[Jaegyun] Jimin.
[Horseking] I need to avoid Jimin.
[Jimin] Let's go.
[♪ epic music playing]
[ZZONE] Come over here.
RED TEAM'S SURPRISE MOTH-TO-FLAME ATTACK
[Pani Bottle grunts]
JOONSU TAGS PANI BOTTLE
[Ddolddol] Tag, tag!
KIM DDOLDDOL TAGS ZZONE
Tag.
-[Jimin] Tag!
-What?
JIMIN TAGS HORSEKING
Hey!
-[alarm blaring]
-[host] Tag confirmed.
[knocks on door]
Hello.
[Ddolddol] Tag, tag!
-[Jimin] Tag!
-[player] Tag.
[host] Tag confirmed.
DDOLDDOL LANDED FIRST TAG
[dealer] We will check
both players' cards.
Please hand in your cards.
The moth-to-flame strategy
worked like a charm.
Next round, we should do it again
and get Jimin to tag Horseking somehow.
This is Kim Ddolddol's card.
[ZZONE] What is happening?
I never thought he'd tag me.
[dealer] ZZONE, please submit your card.
[dealer] ZZONE...
[♪ intense music playing]
...has won.
-This concludes the game.
-[gasps, exclaims]
Checking symbols... Confirmed.
2 HOURS AGO
[shards clatter]
[Jaegyun]
Give us the Shuffle Ticket, please.
Let's go, ZZONE.
[Horseking] Okay.
If we give her 6 to Joonsu
and move around as a group of three,
wouldn't it be safer?
-ZZONE's card?
-[Horseking] The two of them.
We could trust Joonsu
or the two of us could do it.
But having one more person
could be better.
-Ah...
-[Horseking] What do you say?
It's a good idea.
I like that idea.
I'll run around on my own.
It seemed like the better way to go.
I immediately agreed to it.
Joonsu can move around
much more easily than I can.
So, we figured it'd be better
for me to hold onto the Joker
and stay safely hidden.
Horseking's idea was a stroke of genius.
We're going to use our Shuffle Ticket.
[dealer] If you would like
to use a Shuffle Ticket,
please submit your cards.
[♪ triumphant music playing]
JOKER TO ZZONE, 6 TO JOONSU
CARDS SHUFFLED
-[ZZONE] I'm counting on you.
-I'll do my best.
[ZZONE] I'll take good care of it.
[Ddolddol exclaims]
-[ZZONE] Finally, it's over!
-[Ddolddol] Were you the Joker?
[ZZONE] I was.
-[sighs]
-It's over!
[dealer] Blue Team has defeated
Red Team's King card.
This concludes the game.
Oh! I told you!
[cheering]
KINGMAKER
COMES TO AN END AFTER 16 HOURS
So the King ran straight into the Joker.
I really was a moth to a flame. [chuckles]
The moth-to-flame strategy worked,
but the result was a complete disaster.
[laughs]
[mic feedback]
[host] The winner of the Main Match,
"Kingmaker," is the Blue Team.
[all cheering]
We won!
-[Horseking] Good job. [sighs]
-[Joonsu] Good work.
Nice.
[exhales joyfully]
[Joonsu] This is so nice.
-It's finally over.
-[Horseking] This game was long.
I was the one who put this team together.
I felt a lot of pressure.
I thought if we lost, I'd feel so bad
about letting everyone down.
But once we won, all that agony vanished.
Finally, it's over!
[sighs in relief]
It was such a cathartic feeling.
[Jaegyun] We worked so hard
to search for and find the symbols.
I was happy and hadn't felt
that kind of dopamine rush in a while.
[Horseking] The thrill of playing
aggressively and taking the victory
felt like we'd won the whole thing.
-Good work.
-You too.
[Horseking] Starting
with Dail's sacrifice play,
he tagged Yuk Junseo twice.
[chuckling]
[Joonsu] That's not an easy thing to do.
That's so cool.
[Jaegyun] Where's Dail?
I want to tell him the good news.
Oh!
-General Yang!
[Joonsu] General Yang!
-I promised you, didn't I?
-I promised we'd win, didn't I?
[Dail] Ah, this is the happiest
I've been this year. [exhales]
[chuckling]
This is the best day of 2026.
-[Jaegyun] Oh, my.
-[Dail] Oh, my team.
[exclaiming]
[ZZONE] Great work.
We really had a fun time.
-Such a fun time.
-You made it happen.
You made it happen, Dail.
For us, he was such a hero.
[Horseking laughing]
The sacrifice play was a success!
[Dail] They're in serious trouble.
[Joonsu] I know.
[Jaegyun] It's like a funeral over there.
-Hey, man!
-[Pani Bottle] What a shame.
We were close.
-[Horseking] Hey, Joonsu.
-[sighs heavily]
[sighs disappointedly] I'm so damn upset.
-You did everything you could.
-[groans] I'm so upset.
[both sighing]
This is so annoying. [sobs softly]
You did well.
We all did well.
[sniffles]
[groans] I feel bad
for letting Eunsil and Junseo down.
[sniffles]
[Pani Bottle]
We put up a really good fight.
-We lost, but we fought well.
-[sniffles]
Okay?
[Jimin sobbing] Seriously, I'm pissed off.
[exhales] I'm so pissed off.
The moment when you realize
that you can't beat someone,
you feel hopeless and angry.
[♪ pensive music playing]
Good work. I mean it.
You really did great.
[sniffles] We did all we could.
[sobbing]
[voice breaks] Pani Bottle...
This is so annoying.
[sobbing]
[exhales] Seriously...
We went through so much.
You did well. You did amazing.
You couldn't have done anything more.
[sniffles]
You did amazing.
[both sobbing softly]
-I feel terrible.
-No, don't.
[Jimin] If I hadn't been on this team...
[Pani Bottle]
Our team did everything we could.
That's why I cried.
I poured everything I had into this.
-[Joonsu grunts]
-[Jimin] I got you! Tag!
And I was really proud.
We may have lost, but we fought so hard.
So, it was really fun, really intense,
and really tough.
I'm tearing up again.
[♪ pensive music continues playing]
[breathes deeply]
[sniffles]
[voice breaks] Seriously... [exhales]
There were definitely moments
when we could've won.
[exhales]
By the way... [clears throat]
...this is my third reality survival show,
but I don't think I'll ever forget this.
We lost, but I'll never forget this.
Ah, I need to stop crying.
God damn it, I'm 40. What am I doing?
Shit, I'm tearing up.
[sniffles, exhales]
[Jimin breathes deeply]
[sobbing]
[Jimin groans]
[sobs]
[Jimin] We were both crying
like we'd fought for a cause and lost.
Going through that together,
we grew close.
Is my face bleeding?
You're bleeding. And here.
You've got a scratch.
[exhales] I'm so annoyed.
Aren't there any tissues?
Are you hurt?
-Where? How?
-[Jimin] He must've been scratched.
[Ddolddol sighs]
-We're all a mess.
-[Pani Bottle] Good work.
We really did our best until the very end.
-[Jimin] We really did.
-Well done. We did a good job.
We gave it everything we had
and did whatever it took.
Think about it.
We didn't chicken out.
We went for it and took them on.
At the end, we just charged in
and turned the whole thing into chaos.
We were proud.
We were all very brave to the end.
It was the Shuffle Ticket at the end.
[Pani Bottle]
Didn't think ZZONE was the Joker?
At that point, all I could do was think,
"Let's at least take someone out."
I wanted to yank
that pink hair at the end.
[Jimin] You did well. You didn't like
that she took everyone with her.
-I mean...
-[Jimin] From the start...
I knew it as soon as she picked four guys.
Right.
Good work.
I wanted to yank her pink hair so badly
in a leader fight.
[Jimin] One tag was good enough.
We should've battled,
but they kept hiding,
so we never got a chance.
Luck just wasn't on our side.
Let's think that way.
-[Jimin] And we really were neck-and-neck.
-Luck just wasn't on our side.
[Ddolddol] To be fair,
we did really amazing.
Considering our physical abilities,
we've already won.
[Ddolddol] Exactly, we really did amazing.
But once we get to the Death Match,
I swear, I don't think I'll resent
or hold anything against anyone.
No matter who wins and moves on or loses,
I'll be okay with it either way.
I mean it.
[Ddolddol] I felt the same.
If I get eliminated
and our Red Team members make it through,
I'll genuinely be happy for them.
If the Death Match is about politics,
should we take out Sanghyun first?
[cackling]
If it involves politics,
let's get rid of him first.
-Sanghyun has to go.
-[Pani Bottle] Then rock, paper, scissors.
If I do that,
I'll be the worst traitor ever.
No, you won't be.
-Still, I should, right?
-[Pani Bottle] Yes.
You've already betrayed people before.
-I mean, I was with the Red Team just now.
-[cackling]
Sanghyun isn't technically our family.
He's a stranger.
Being a prisoner
and being eliminated are different.
[Pani Bottle] Who cares?
I need to save myself first.
-[Ddolddol laughs]
-Send him off.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Sanghyun was unfairly sent to prison
because I rallied everyone
to think he was the Seeker.
Now, we've come face-to-face
in the Death Match.
[Sanghyun groans]
I know he's been through a lot,
and he's done so well,
so he can go home to get some rest.
They say you always meet
your enemies in the Death Match.
[Sanghyun] I'm going to wipe everyone out
and win the game.
-[Ddolddol] This time...
-[Pani Bottle] Let's eliminate Sanghyun.
Even if it's dirty,
let's do what it takes.
[host] This Death Match
is an auction game.
[Jimin] An auction?
-One million won.
-10 million won.
-I bid 40 million.
-50 million.
I bid 70 million.
I bid 80 million.
[Sanghyun] The prison players
were starting to get on my nerves.
[Ddolddol] It's all about momentum.
[Sanghyun] What is this?
This is really bad.
[♪ tense music playing]
[Ddolddol] Goodbye, Sanghyun.
[mic feedback]
[host] The top two players
in this Main Match
will advance straight to the finals.
[gasps in awe]
[Dail] I'll do whatever it takes
to go to the finals.
[Jaegyun] I'm absolutely confident.
[Horseking] Come here.
[grunting]
[ZZONE] I'll be hiding.
[Joonsu] I've got to survive and win.
Where is everyone?
Let's take out the ones who are hiding.
We should, but I can't fucking find them.
-There you are.
-[Jaegyun exclaims]
-Hey.
-[Horseking] You're dead meat.
[Dail groans] For fuck's sake.
[♪ ominous music playing]
Translated by Youji Kim